{"response_code":0,"results":[{"category":"Entertainment: Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"Who is Batman?","correct_answer":"Bruce Wayne","incorrect_answers":["Clark Kent","Barry Allen","Tony Stark"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"Who is the creator of the comic series &quot;The Walking Dead&quot;?","correct_answer":"Robert Kirkman","incorrect_answers":["Stan Lee","Malcolm Wheeler-Nicholson","Robert Crumb"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Comics","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Deadpool&#039;s identity is Slade Wilson.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Comics","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"The &quot;Pepe&quot; meme originated from a comic drawn by Matt Furie called &quot;Boy&#039;s Club&quot;?","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"This Marvel superhero is often called &quot;The man without fear&quot;.","correct_answer":"Daredevil","incorrect_answers":["Thor","Wolverine","Hulk"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"Which universe crossover was introduced in the &quot;Sonic the Hedgehog&quot; comic issue #247?","correct_answer":"Mega Man","incorrect_answers":["Super Mario Brothers","Alex Kidd","Super Monkey Ball"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"What is the alter-ego of the DC comics character &quot;Superman&quot;?","correct_answer":"Clark Kent","incorrect_answers":["Bruce Wayne","Arthur Curry","John Jones"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"What is the full first name of the babysitter in Calvin and Hobbes?","correct_answer":"Rosalyn","incorrect_answers":["Rose","Ruby","Rachel"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"The main six year old protagonist in Calvin and Hobbes is named after what theologian?","correct_answer":"John Calvin","incorrect_answers":["Calvin Klein","Calvin Coolidge","Phillip Calvin McGraw"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"In &quot;Homestuck&quot; what is Dave Strider&#039;s guardian?","correct_answer":"Bro","incorrect_answers":["Becquerel","Doc Scratch","Halley"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"In &quot;Homestuck&quot; the &quot;Kingdom of Darkness&quot; is also known as?","correct_answer":"Derse","incorrect_answers":["Skaia","Prospit","The Medium"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"When was Marvel Comics founded?","correct_answer":"1939","incorrect_answers":["1932","1951","1936"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"In Black Hammer, what city did the heroes save from the Anti-God?","correct_answer":"Spiral City","incorrect_answers":["Mega-City One","Rockwood","Star City"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"What&#039;s the race of Invincible&#039;s father?","correct_answer":"Viltrumite","incorrect_answers":["Kryptonian","Kree","Irken"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"Which one of these superhero teams appears in the Invincible comics?","correct_answer":"Guardians of the Globe","incorrect_answers":["Avengers","Justice League","Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles"]}]}